In this video, we will learn how to use the AI sticker generator.
Entering the keyword will allow you to create a sticker based on your choice, and you can actually check the effect in the 3D window.
Before running the AI sticker generator, please add a sticker to the costume first.
By adjusting the sticker tool, select the sticker that needs to be replaced with the picture.
In the sticker attribute, click the AI sticker generator button on the default side.
The AI sticker generator window will pop up.
In the options at the top of the dialogue window, you can set the type of the picture and whether to open the transparent background, then enter the keyword.
Below the keyword is the final picture generated.
In the history record window,
you can see the history record of the picture,
and the previous picture generated.
At the top of each picture in the history record,
you can see the selected options and keywords for generating this picture.
The history record will remain before you close Marvelous Designer.
Next, let's take a look at the various options of the AI sticker generator.
You can select the style category of the pattern in the pattern category.
Under the art style, you can select the specific sticker art style.
If you do not need to specify any special art style,
you can select no.
If you choose a transparent background,
the background of the sticker generated is transparent.
Please note that you cannot generate a transparent background art sticker.
Now let's enter the keyword and start generating the sticker.
When you enter the keyword,
using the English keyword will help you generate more accurate pictures.
click the generate button to generate a picture.
The generated pictures are continuous in all directions.
The AI sticker generator generates pictures randomly every time.
Therefore, even if the keywords are the same,
the results of the generation are also diverse.
When entering keywords,
we recommend that you use words,
not long sentences,
and long sentences to describe them.
Long sentences may lead to incorrect results.
It is recommended that you use words and keywords to define keywords.
If you want to emphasize a keyword,
please emphasize it with a keyword.
The keywords in the keyword will give more weight.
When you use a keyword once,
its weight will be 1.1 times.
When you use a keyword twice,
its weight will be 1.2 times.
You can see that different keywords will have different results.
When you want to generate a picture randomly,
click the random icon in the investment form,
and the random icon will set and set keywords randomly.
By setting randomly,
you can create various types of pictures,
enriching your creation.
When you want to generate a new picture similar to the previous result,
or want to update some keywords,
please click the Keep Keywords button.
When you click Create,
you can see that the generated picture is similar to the previous one.
Please note that if you modify keywords,
the results may be due to the addition or modification of keywords
that are different from the previous generated pictures.
You may need to generate a picture for a certain time,
so you can click the arrow button in the upper right corner to fold the window.
When waiting for the picture to be created, you can continue to adjust the costume or other changes.
When the picture is created, the foldable window will remind you that the picture has been created.
If you need to open the window, click the arrow in the upper right corner again.
When the picture is created, click the application button at the bottom.
You can also go to the history record and use the previous picture as a sticker.
You can add more interesting content to your design through this function.
Thank you for watching, see you in the next video.